女士们  先生们 容我第一次这样称呼
Ladies and gentlemen, for the first time ever
马修・埃里克森和莉莉・奥德林夫妇
Mr. and Marshall Eriksen and Lily Aldrin.
我们没有用同一个姓氏 你是不是有点伤心?
Does it make you kind of sad that we don't share the same last name?
在21世纪的今天来看
You know, in a totally evolved 21st-century kind of way,
是有一点儿
yeah, a little.
你知道我们该做什么
You know what we should do?
我们应该用一个全新的姓
We should come up with a whole new last name.
这个容易 莉莉和马修・斯凯沃克
Oh, that's easy-- Lily and Marshall Skywalker.
莉莉和马修・哈斯霍夫
Lily and Marshall Hasselhoff.
我想到一个  要听吗
I got it. You ready?
- 准备好了? - 嗯
- You ready? - Yeah.
莉莉和马修・欧森 (指两人为绝配)
Lily and Marshall Awesome.
你碰见欧森夫妇了?
Have you met the Awesomes?
马修  莉莉  他们的儿子 当然还有女儿  弗里金
Marshall, Lily, their son, Totally and their daughter, Freakin'?
我爱你  欧森先生
I love you, Mr. Awesome.
我爱你  欧森夫人
I love you, Mrs. Awesome.
- 那么... - 怎样
- So... - So...
婚礼结束了
Wedding's over.
是的
Yes, it is.
我想明天
I guess starting tomorrow,
我们可以跟别人宣布了
we can tell people.
宣布什么?
Tell people what?
你好  巴尼
Hi, Barney.
宣布什么?
Tell people what?
那些食物看起来很好吃
The food looks delicious, doesn't it?
宣布什么?
Tell people what?
没什么
Nothing.
好了  宣布什么?
Oh, okay. Tell people what?
我们晚点儿再谈这个话题好吗?
Can we talk about this later?
那不行  到底宣布什么?
Absolutely. Tell people what?
你见过巴尼吗
- Hi. Have you met Barney? - Hey. Barney Stinson.
你好  巴尼・斯汀森
衣服很漂亮
Lovely dress. I know, I'm sick of these things, too.
我也对这种事情厌烦透了
就像同一个婚礼重复一遍又一遍  你完全说对了
It's like the same wedding over and over again. You're totally right.
要跳舞吗? 好极了  舞池上见
You want to dance? Great, see you out there. Tell people what?
宣布什么?
我们现在不想谈论这个话题 好吗  巴尼?
Look, this is just not something we want to talk about right now, okay, Barney?
好吧
Okay.
差点儿包不住了
Whoo, that was a close one.
你想他会就这么算了吗?
Think he'll actually let it go?
宣布什么?宣布什么?宣布什么?
Tell people what? Tell people what? Tell people what?
宣布什么?宣布...
Tell people what? Tell people...
停车场有一辆黑色尼桑没有关车灯
There's a black Nissan Stanza in the parking lot with it's lights on.
宣布什么?宣布什么?
Tell people what? Tell people what?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
Subtitles : Willow's Team
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第二十二集
Transcript : Raceman
翻译：    沙萱         校对：     叶煦
www.forom.com
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
请给我一杯水
Can I get a water please?
- 宣布什么? - 天呐  好吧
- Tell people what? - Oh, God! Okay.
我们是有些...事情要说
Look, we have some... news.
但今天是莉莉和马修的好日子 我们不想让大家把视线从他们身上挪开
But we don't want to draw attention away from Lily and Marshall's big day.
所以别再提这事了 等他们去度蜜月了再说
So just forget about it until they leave for the honeymoon.
好吧
Fine.
- 那可是个惊人的消息 -上帝啊  快告诉我
- It's pretty big, though. - Oh, my God, just tell me!
- 帮帮我们 - 怎么了
- Oh, help us. - What's wrong?
我快饿死了
We're starving.
我们让酒店安排了 这么美味的食品
We planned this amazing meal with the caterers,
可我们还一口都没吃上
and we haven't had a bite of it.
每次刚想吃总会被鸡尾酒代替
Every time we get near the food, we get cocktail weiner blocked.
马修
Marshall!
我们一整天都没吃东西了
We haven't eaten all day.
我们来想想办法
All right, let's run some interference.
让你们能安稳的坐到餐桌上去
Yeah, we'll get you back to your table. Come on.
你们在这里
Oh, there you are.
亲爱的  你真漂亮
My dear, you look so beautiful.
谢谢  格兰 我们正打算...
Thanks, Grammie, but we really need to...
还有你... 看起来就像四十年代的电影明星
And you... you look like a 1940s movie star.
你看起来就象撒上胡椒粉的烤小羊 再配上薄荷果冻
And you look like a pepper-crusted rack of lamb with mint jelly.
让他俩去吃点东西
All right, let's get these two back to their table.
一会你们会一起来跳康迦舞?
We will see you on the floor for the conga line later, won't we?
那个问题早在几周前就有答案了
The answer to that one was decided weeks earlier.
几周前
康迦舞
Conga line.
当然
Oh, yes, definitely.
放一段展现你们俩 这些年生活片段的幻灯片怎么样
How about a slide show of you guys through the years
就像格林・德的作品《你们的日子》 (摇滚乐队)
set to Green Day's "Time of Your Life"
以你们孩子一张张的照片为结尾
and ending with your baby photos side by side.
棒极了  记到清单上
Oh, that's great. Going on the list.
什么清单
What list?
传统的  土气的东西 在我的婚礼上统统不要
Horrible wedding clichs we're not going to touch with a ten-foot limbo pole.
就像First Corinthians (古典音乐)?
Oh, like First Corinthians?
圣经诗歌?
That Bible verse?
每个婚礼上都会颂读的
They do that at every wedding.
什么内容?
How's it go?
爱  是忍耐和宽容
"Love is patient and kind.
爱  不能嫉妒和炫耀
"Love does not envy or boast.
也不是傲慢和粗鲁
"It is not arrogant or rude.
爱  不会固执己见
"Love does not insist on it's own way.
不急躁  也不怨恨
"It is not irritable or resentful.
爱  承担一切
"Love bears all things,
相信一切
"believes all things,
憧憬一切
"hopes all things...
忍耐一切
"endures all things."
- 老土 - 记到清单上
- Lame. - Going on the list.
我们做到了一个 新奇而有趣的婚礼
We've done it. A wedding with zero clichs.
难道说在大厅里举行婚礼 不是传统做法?
Wait, isn't doing it in the reception hall bathroom kind of a clich?
好吧  就这一项?
Well, okay, one clich?
严格说来  是两项
Well, technically two.
不  他们又把盘子收走了!
No! They cleared our plates again!
撒了胡椒粉的烤羊肉 你到哪里去了?!
Pepper-crusted rack of lamb, where did you go?!
在我的新婚之夜应该有你相伴的
It's my wedding night. I was supposed to have my way with you.
别伤心了  你还有我
Well, you still have me.
是...
Yeah...
事实上我们正在讨论一些事情
Anyway, guys, we're kind of in the middle of something,
所以你们要么滚一边淌口水去 要么去享受一份无性但紧张的宁静
so if you could go bicker or share a tense, sexless silence
或者做一些已婚人士该做的事 那就最好不过了
or whatever married people do somewhere else, that'd be great.
不  巴尼 这可是我的婚礼
No, Barney, this is my wedding,
我想坐哪儿就坐哪儿
and I will sit wherever I damn well...
那是些小蛋饼吗
Are those mini quiches?
快说  什么秘密
Tell the secret.
好吧...
Okay, uh...
在我们交往一周年纪念日
it was our anniversary,
我们去了卡尔麦可餐厅
so we went to this restaurant Carmichael's,
就是我们第一次约会的地方
which is where we went on our first date.
在那里我为罗宾偷了蓝色的法国号
Remember, the place where I stole the blue French horn for Robin?
原来是你
Oh, right, that was you.
我就知道是我认识的什么人
I knew that was somebody I knew.
什么
What?
老兄  你明明在那里
Dude, you were there.
那是我们生命里 一个值得记住的时刻
That was like a big iconic moment in all of our lives.
对你来说可能是 我可有一大堆精彩的故事
Maybe in your life-- I got a lot of stuff going on.
我们正坐着  侍者过来了...
Okay, so we're sitting there and the waiter comes over...
香槟?
Champagne?
我们没点香槟
Um, we didn't order champagne.
餐厅致以特别祝贺
Compliments of the house.
Wow.
多谢
Thanks.
干杯
Cheers.
就在我的香槟杯底
And there, sitting at the bottom of my champagne glass is...
小蛋饼
Mini quiche.
你这个大混蛋
You're a mega-douche.
他们把那张桌子搬回厨房了
Oh, that's right, they moved that table back toward the kitchen,
因为他们要在那里做巧克力喷泉 给你们一个惊喜
because that's where they're setting up a surprise chocolate fountain.
我说漏嘴了...
Oh, no, I gave it away.
杯子里有什么?
So what was in the glass?
对了
Right.
侍者拿着两杯酒过来
So the waiter comes up with two glasses of Dom.
他说香槟?我们没点香槟
He says, "Champagne?" "We didn't order any champagne."
餐厅致以特别祝贺
"Compliments of the house." "Wow."
那些你已经说过了!
You said that already!
罗宾往里一看
Right. So Robin looks down,
就在她的杯子里
and there at the bottom of her glass...
有一枚订婚戒指
Is an engagement ring.
想对新郎新娘说点什么?
Anything you want to say to the bride and groom?
千万不要结婚
Don't get married.
我一会再来好了
Why don't I come back.
订婚戒指?
An engagement ring?
不...不...
No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
你不能这样对我  不行
Ted, you cannot do this to me. No.
不  不  绝对不行!
No, no, no!
那正是她说的话
That's what she said.
不
No.
不...不...泰德 你不能这样对我
No, no, no, no, no. Ted, you cannot do this to me.
不  万万不要
No. No, no, no.
你在说些什么?
What are you talking about?
这个...这就是我在说的 它怎么会在我的香槟里?
This. This is what I'm talking about. What is this doing in my champagne?
我得离开这里
Oh, God, listen... I just got to get out of here.
那不是我的
That's not mine.
什么
What?
那不是我的戒指
That's not mine.
那是谁的
Then whose is it?
是我的
It's mine.
詹娜...
Janna...
愿意嫁给我吗
will you marry me?
是的
Yes.
Wow.
真是一出闹剧 我好像有点...
That was hilarious. I was like... what?
算了
Anyway.
那是怎么了
What the hell was that?
什么怎么了
What the hell was what?
那种反应?
That reaction?
我以为你在向我求婚
I thought you were proposing to me.
就这样?听起来就像 是我要把你往火坑里推
Really? Because it sounded like you thought I was trying to set you on fire.
你知道我对婚姻的态度
Ted, you know how I feel about marriage.
现在更清楚了
Now more than ever.
对不起 你本计划今晚求婚吗
I'm sorry, were you planning on proposing tonight?
没有
No.
那为什么这么介意
Then why is this an issue?
因为我在想 我们在一起已经一年了
Because even though you don't want to get married,
我们彼此相爱 就算你不想结婚
I'd like to think the fact that we've been together for a year,
也应该是个稍微温和点的反应
and that we love each other might get me a gentler reaction
而不是  不...不...
than, "No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你不能这样对我
"Ted, you cannot do this to me.
不...不...
"No. No, no, no."
你说得对我反应过度了
Okay, you're right, I just... freaked out.
我也不知道为什么
I don't know why.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们别把它放在心上好吗
Can we please just let it go?
我做不到
No.
斯汀森
Hey, Stinson.
别再说那些巧克力喷泉的谎话
Never lie to a man about a chocolate fountain.
那你们找到什么吃的了吗
So did you guys find anything to eat?
我吃了4个草莓
I had four strawberries.
是不是在每个草莓还带着一杯香槟酒?
Was there a side of champagne with each of the strawberries?
正是
Yes.
莉莉你可以打嗝 或是回答  是的
Lily, you could have burped or said the word "Yes,"
可你两样一起做 那正是我娶你的原因
but the fact that you did both is exactly why I married you.
看  还有好多草莓
Oh, look, more strawberries!
后来怎样了?
So what happened next?
- 泰德  别这样 - 不  我是认真的
- Ted, don't do this. - No, seriously.
你觉得你今后五年会在哪儿?
Where do you see yourself in five years?
那你呢?
Where do you see yourself?
老实说今后五年...
Honestly, in five years...
我或许已经结婚了
I probably want to be married.
可我很可能去了阿根廷
And I probably want to be in Argentina.
- 阿根廷? - 或者东京或是巴黎
- Argentina? - Or Tokyo, or Paris.
听我说  泰德 我不知道五年后我在哪里
Look, Ted, I don't know where I'm going to be in five years.
我也不想知道 我希望生活充满冒险
And I don't want to know. I want my life to be an adventure.
我们的关系结束了?
We have an expiration date, don't we?
天呐
Oh, my God.
你们分手了
You guys broke up.
你们竟然分手了简直不敢相信
You guys broke up. I can't believe it.
巴尼...
Barney...
故事还没有结束
story's not over.
我们能不能不要 在这里谈这个话题?回家再说不好吗?
Can we please not talk about this here. Can we go home?
是的  当然可以
Yeah, of course.
不好意思  我们能不能...
Uh, excuse me, I'm sorry about this. Can we actually...
上帝啊  是你
Oh, my God, it's you.
我...什么?
Wha... what?
就是你这狗杂种 偷了我们的蓝色法国号
You're the son of a bitch who stole our blue French horn.
快跑!
Run!
跑?你的计策就是逃跑?
Run? Your strategy was run?
这是个完美的办法
It was a perfectly good idea.
他们又没有我们的信用卡资料
They didn't have our credit card information.
他们根本不认识我们
They didn't know us from Adam.
我是这么打算的
I stand by it.
是吗
Yeah?
那结果怎样了?
And how did that work out for you?
我不明白为什么他们 要扣下我的信用卡和驾照
I don't see why they had to keep my credit card and driver's license
直到我们把号送回来
till we bring the horn back.
得了吧  这也能怨他们?
Well, come on, Ted, can you blame them?
对不起 我很抱歉拿了法国号
Look, I'm sorry about the French horn.
我希望还能弥补这事
I want to make this right.
我们现在最好是... 跑!
So what we're going to do right now is, we're going to run!
那么...阿根廷?
So... Argentina.
阿根廷
Argentina.
怎么以前从没听你提过阿根廷?
Why is this the first I've heard of Argentina?
看来美国的学校地理教得太烂了
Mmm, American schools suck at geography.
告诉你我想去阿根廷重要吗
What would be the point in telling you that I want to live in Argentina?
你不想住这里
You don't want to live there.
我也可以在阿根廷生活
I could want to live in Argentina.
不  你不行
No, you couldn't.
你的生活  你的事业都在这里
I mean, you life is here and your career.
我是记者  我的工作 决定了我可能去任何地方
I'm a journalist, my career could take me anywhere,
我也希望这样
and I hope it does.
我也可以去任何地方  做为建筑师
Hey. I could be an architect anywhere, too.
阿根廷也有不少建筑
They have buildings in Argentina.
还有巴黎  甚至东京
And Paris. And even Tokyo.
我不知道你有没有看过哥斯拉 可他也不会去掀翻没撑开的账蓬
I don't know if you ever saw Godzilla, but he wasn't knocking down a bunch of tents.
什么意思?你在说 你愿意搬到阿根廷去?
So, what? You're saying you want to move to Argentina?
我总为大学期间没能 花一年时间出国看看感到遗憾
Well, I always regretted not taking a year in college to live abroad.
我刚刚完成一个大工程
I just finished a big project at work.
存了些钱
I got some money saved up.
如果我生命中 有段时间想要这么做 那就是现在
If ever there were a time in my life to do something like this, it's right now.
我们搬到阿根廷去
Let's move to Argentina.
别说了
Oh, shut up.
你感到吃惊?我没有开玩笑
You're scared I might not be kidding.
是吗
Aren't you?
没有
Nope.
去吧  特布罗斯基
Your move, Scherbatsky.
好吧
Okay.
就这么办 一起搬到阿根廷去
Let's do it-- let's move to Argentina.
不  难以置信
No es posible!
没人会去阿根廷
Nobody moves to Argentina.
阿根廷比索五年内贬值三分之二
The Argentinean peso has dropped two-thirds in five years,
政府反对自由贸易的改革
the government is opposed to free market reforms,
铁道部门罢工后 铁路交通也一片混乱
and the railroad has been a mess since the breakup of Ferrocarriles Argentinos.
我在扬基体育馆旁边
I hooked up with an Argentinean exchange student
钓到过一名阿根廷交换生
in a Porta-John outside Yankee Stadium.
她特别健谈
Man, she was chatty.
怎么样  怎么样
Right? Right?
你接到了新娘捧花?
You caught the bouquet?
巴尼
Barney.
故事还在继续
The story's not over yet.
- 等等  等等 - 怎么了
- Wait, wait, wait, wait. - What?
我不知道该不该这么做
I don't know if I can do this to you.
做什么?
Do what?
你说愿意搬去阿根廷
Well, you say you want to move to Argentina,
可你想要孩子
but you want to have kids.
没错儿  那里没有孩子
Oh, right. 'Cause there are no kids there.
在圣诞老人的地图上 阿根廷是一个大黑X
On Santa's map of the world, there's a big black "X" over Argentina.
- 你懂我的意思 - 不  我懂
- You know what I mean. - No, I don't.
好吧  假定我们有了孩子
Okay, say we had kids.
他们也不一定要在农村长大
They wouldn't have to grow up in some suburb somewhere.
他们也可以 跟我们一起过冒险的生活
They would grow up on the road having adventures with us.
想想看他们能 收集多少"硬石咖啡"的T恤
Think of all the Hard Rock Cafe T-shirts they could collect.
你知道我从来没想过要孩子
Ted, you know that kids were never a part of my plan.
但是如果有一天我想要孩子了
But if I was going to have someone's babies,
那一定是你的
I'd have your babies.
是时候逃跑了
That's when you run.
快说你跑掉了  泰德
Tell me you ran, Ted.
等等  等等 我们可不想现在就要小孩
Wait, wait, wait. We don't want to start having babies right this second.
你有没有...?
Do you have a...?
不  没有
No, I don't.
也许我们不该继续
Well, we probably shouldn't.
是啊
Yeah.
- 赌一次? - 赌一次
- Risk it? - Risk it.
不
No.
女士们  先生们 都到这里来
All right, ladies and gentlemen, if you're all gather around,
下面莉莉和马修要切蛋糕了
Lily and Marshall are going to cut the cake.
不  罗宾  你该不是...
No. Robin, you're not...
不  快跟我说故事还没结束
No, say the story's not over.
快点  切蛋糕了
Come on, they're cutting the cake.
快说故事还没完!
Say the story's not over!
上帝  有人怀孕了 这是我碰到的第12件让人烦心的事了
Oh, God, this is the 12th most worried I've ever been that someone's pregnant.
别闹了  莉莉
Okay, Lily.
我真的饿了  千万瞄准 好不好?
I'm really hungry, so let's just, uh, aim for my mouth, okay?
还有  蛋糕的污渍很难洗  记得吗
Besides, the smearing the cake thing's a clich? remember?
不  那样才有趣
No, it's going to be so funny.
莉莉
Lily.
莉莉  快把蛋糕扔我嘴里
Lily, just feed me the cake.
求你了  宝贝  我饿死了
Please, baby, I am so hungry.
嗯  很好
Whoopsy-daisy.
她没事
And she's okay.
- 她很好 - 只是个玩笑
- She's all right. - That was funny.
现在该去渡蜜月了
And it's time for the honeymoon.
各位  多谢你们
Guys, guys, guys. Thank you so much.
我们爱你
We love you.
我也爱你们
I love you.
结婚生子
Getting married, having kids.
完全是个错误  可怕的错误
It's all a mistake. It's a horrible, horrible mistake.
这家伙完全没有建设性
God, this guy's giving me nothing.
在苏格兰玩开心点
All right, have fun in Scotland.
如果见到尼斯湖水怪 就说泰德向他问好
If you see the Loch Ness Monster, tell him Ted Mosby says, "What's up?"
尼斯水怪是女性 泰德  别忘了
Nessie's a she, Ted, come on.
老兄
Hey, kiddo.
你会被一大堆 家庭琐事缠得脱不开身
You are going to miss out on a lot of awesome stuff.
当我在外面逍遥快活时
You'll be at home with the kid
你还得在家看孩子
while I am out awesome-ing all over the place.
还有你  会变成个肥婆
And you're going to get fat.
故事还没完呢  巴尼
The story's not over, Barney.
是时候把法国号还给那餐馆了
Okay, time to get the horn back to the bistro.
我不知道是不是 能再来一次  我累坏了
Oh, Ted, I don't know if I can go again. That tuckered me out.
我不是指那个
Not a euphemism.
那好吧  等我换件衣服 我们这就去
Right. Okay, let me just go change, and we'll leave.
你要换衣服  我不用吗
Whoa, whoa, you get to change and I don't? Uh-uh.
有点团队精神  小姐
Solidarity, sister.
那可不行  我有换洗衣服 你却没有  得了吧
That is crazy. I have a change of clothes and you don't. Suck it up.
如果我们要共同生活 我的生活用品就应试应该在这里
Well, if we'd actually moved in together, all my stuff would be here,
可我们没有所以...
but we didn't, so...
是啊
Yeah.
我们只是说说而已?
We were all talk, weren't we?
我们没法在一起了?
We're not doing this, are we?
我不想在阿根廷生孩子
I don't want to have kids in Argentina.
我更不想
And I don't want to have kids in Argentina.
那我们该何去何从?
So where does that leave us?
也许...
Well...
我们还是可以一起生活...
we could stay together and...
假装这些事情都不会发生
pretend this stuff doesn't matter.
或者...
Or...
我们把法国号还回去
we could give back the blue French horn.
你为我偷来的蓝色法国号
You stole a blue French horn for me.
我愿意为你偷整个乐队
I would have stolen you a whole orchestra.
你们确实分手了?
You did break up.
不错
Yep.
你也没有怀孕?
You're not pregnant?
没有
Nope.
马修和莉莉还一无所知?
An-And Marshall and Lily don't know?
后来  我们过来想要告诉你们
Well, afterwards, uh, we came by to tell you guys,
可莉莉实在压力很大
but Lily was pretty stressed out, so...
我们决定在婚礼结束前什么也不说
We decided not to say anything till after the wedding.
你们还好吧
You guys okay?
这两周当然不会好过 不过...
Well, it hasn't been the easiest two weeks of our lives, but...
我们还挺得住
But we're okay.
多亏了那酒吧
The open bar helps.
打扰了  女士
- Excuse me, Miss. - Hi.
能请你跳支舞吗
Could I have this dance?
我们都知道这一天终究会来
Well, we knew this day would come eventually.
照顾好她  小绅士
Take care of her, little man.
这是目前为止 你醉得最厉害的一次了
This is by far the drunkest I've ever seen you.
司机
Uh, driver.
Hello!
瑞吉
Ranjit.
回酒店之前能先停一下吗
Hey, can we make a stop before we head back to the hotel?
不用停
You do not have to stop.
你们可以就在后座上办事
You can be together as man and wife right back there,
我是好哥们儿
and because we are friends...
我不会偷看的
I will not watch.
不  事实上 我们有别的事要办
Um, no, we actually had something else in mind.
当然
Okay.
莉莉  去坐下
Lily, go sit down.
欢迎来到维勒饼屋
Welcome to Wienerburger.
Hi.
我要1号餐  别加泡菜
Can we get a number one, please, with no pickles?
再来一个4号餐  不要洋葱
And a number four with no onions.
让我猜一下 刚参加完杰斐逊高级舞会?
Let me guess. Jefferson High prom?
不
No.
不过谢谢你
But thank you.
其实  我们刚刚结婚了
Actually, we just got married.
- 恭喜了 - 谢谢
- Wow. Congratulations. - Thank you.
7.80美元
That's $7.80.
- 老兄 - 什么
- Hey, dude. - Yeah.
我不知道怎么说才好 你妻子刚刚吐到垃圾箱里了
I don't know how to say this, but your wife just threw up in the trash.
我的妻子
My wife.
马修和莉莉终成眷属
So Marshall and Lily were married,
罗宾和我却分道扬飙
and Robin and I were broken up.
那时候的确很难过
And as hard as it was at the time,
最终我们还是选择了忠于自己
in the end we both got what we wanted.
她如愿去了阿根廷
She did eventually go on to live in Argentina
摩洛哥  希腊还有俄罗斯
and Morocco and Greece, Russia,
甚至在日本小住一段时间
even Japan for a little while.
而我  则遇到了你们的老妈
And I... well, I met your mom.
我深刻地认识到 如果你知道自己想要什么样的生活
I think for the most part if you're really honest with yourself
并且诚实面对自己的心意
about what you want out of life,
那么你会得到想要的一切
life gives it to you.
当然  在那一刻 我其实想要一杯威士忌加苏打
Of course, at that moment, all I really wanted was a scotch and soda
再来支雪茄
and a cigar.
你和罗宾的事我真的很遗憾
I'm really sorry about you and Robin.
我平时总到处开玩笑 希望你们俩分手
I know I was always joking around about wanting you two to break up,
可说实话你们是天生一对
but you were really good together.
是的...
Yeah...
的确
we were.
只是她不是 命中注定的那一个  你懂吗?
She just wasn't the one, you know?
注定的  泰德  够了
The one. Oh, Ted, no.
别又跟我说你要重新开始寻找真爱了
Do not tell me you're going to start searching for "the one" again.
只有当我听说你找到注定的那个的时候
The only time I want to hear you saying "the one"
再跟我说什么 "姻缘天定"的鬼话  怎么样
is if it's followed by the word "hundredth." What up?
不  我要摆脱这一切
No, I need a break from all that, I...
我要离开这里 去找点乐子  明白吗
I just want to get out there and have fun for a while, you know?
是吗
Really?
因为...
'Cause...
你知道吗?你们恋爱已经一年了
you know, you've been in a relationship for a year.
你已经有点迟钝了
You're going to... be a little rusty.
- 没错 - 我是说
- Yeah. - I'm just saying...
你会需要 需要一点点帮助
you're gonna need, need, need some help out there.
可能吧
Could be.
泰德?
Ted?
干嘛  巴尼
Yes, Barney.
你有没有觉得...
Do you think...
也许你...
Do you think maybe you might...
又需要一个搭档了?
need a wingman again?
是的
I do.
太好了
Yes!
是的  我们又回到从前了
Yes! We're back.
我们回去了
We are back.
泰德  好小子 我们会成为传奇...
And Ted, my boy, it's going to be legend...
Wait for it.